

IIRO RITOLA

BACHELOR OF BUSINESS ADMINISTRATION IN **INTERNATIONAL BUSINESS**



PERSONAL PROFILE



I graduated from Vaasa University of Applied Sciences with experience in export, sales, market research and marketing.

I have also always been into technology and I recently studied basics of HTML, CSS, JavaScript and Python coding through Codeacademy.com.

CONTACT S



- Ilmarinkatu 27 B10, **33500 TAMPERE**
- iiro.ritola@netikka.fi
- +358 40 526 1287
- /iiroritola

WORK EXPERIENCE



Temp-Team Finland Oy, Tampere, Sales Representative

FEB 2018 - AUG 2018

- Cold calling potential new B2B customers
- Maintaining current customer relationships
- Understanding the needs of different industries
- Introducing potential candidates to our customers

Atria Scandinavia, Stockholm, Export Coordinator

JUN 2017 - AUG 2017

- Internship
- Conducting macro market research
- Scanning the production capacity in comparison to sales potential and ROI
- Reporting and presenting my findings to the managers
- Thesis including micro market research, which was conducted in the United Kingdom

EDUCATION 😭

Vaasa University of Applied Sciences, BBA in International Business, 2017

LANGUAGES

- Finnish: Native
- English: Full professional proficiency
- Swedish: Limited working proficiency
- German: Basic courses doneFrench: Basic courses done

QUALIFICATIONS



- Hygiene proficiency certificate
- Drivers license class: B
- MS Office
- Visma Nova
- SAP
- Visma Saima

REFERENCES \diamondsuit

Temp-Team Finland

Mika Stenman Business Director mika.stenman@temp-team.fi +358 40 017 4485

Atria Scandinavia

Mats Hallstensson Senior Vice President at PL& Export mats.hallstensson@atria.com +46 70 811 03 20

Face2face, Helsinki, Sales Promoter

JUN 2016 - JUL 2016

- Direct selling B2C
- Responsive way of selling
- Reaching weekly sales goals

Rautia/K-maatalous Saarnio Oy, Jalasjärvi, Warehouse Worker

APR 2015 - JUL 2015

- Warehousing
- Customer service
- Delivering and picking up items

Pihaviriä Oy, Jalasjärvi, Handyman

JAN 2010 - DEC 2014

- Part-time
- Daily farming routines

SKILLS

- Exceptional communication and networking skills
- · Attention to detail and analytical skills
- The ability to work under pressure and multitask